<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Taichi Nakashima</title>
    <link>https://deeeet.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Taichi Nakashima</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja-jp</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-2020 Taichi Nakashima</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 16:41:22 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://deeeet.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2021 Year in Review</title>
      <link>https://deeeet.com/posts/2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 16:41:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeeet.com/posts/2021/</guid>
      <description>Work I continue working at Mercari, Inc.
One of the biggest changes in this year was I changed my role from the individual contributor (IC) to the engineering manager (EM). I’ve been the IC role in all of my carrier and recently worked as Staff plus role. Actually, I was thinking to continue to strive IC path, but, since I got the good opportunity, I decided to take the new role and try new area (another reason is, as The Engineer/Manager Pendulum described, it’s important to do both to be a good lead and I agreed on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSE 138: Distributed Systems</title>
      <link>https://deeeet.com/posts/cse-138/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 11:46:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeeet.com/posts/cse-138/</guid>
      <description>From the beginning of this year, I started to take lecture courses of undergrad distributed systems course at UC Santa Cruz (CSE 138) by Lindsey Kuper. It consists of 23 lectures (you can see the schedule of topics from here) and recently I&amp;rsquo;ve finished all of them. I&amp;rsquo;m not a student at UCSC but due to the COVID-19 situation, all these lectures were delivered online and are available on YouTube. So I was able to take them (Read about the background of online lecture and setup of it on Twitch plays CSE138).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020 Year in Review</title>
      <link>https://deeeet.com/posts/2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 17:35:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeeet.com/posts/2020/</guid>
      <description>I wrote these in Japanese in the past but, from this year, I switched it to English. Here is the summary of what went on in my jobs and life.
Work I continue working for the platform team at Mercari, Inc.
One of the biggest projects I worked on this year was to re-organize the platform team. Originally, when we started the platform team, it consisted of only 3 members. After 3 years, the team grew to more than 10 members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practices for Better Terraform Module</title>
      <link>https://deeeet.com/posts/practices-for-better-terraform-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 22:03:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeeet.com/posts/practices-for-better-terraform-module/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been working at the internal platform team at Mercari for 3 years. In that team, we’ve developed and provided the special Terraform module, which bootstraps required infrastructure and SaaS services for building one microservice, to internal developers (See more details on Terraform Ops for Microservices). Now, this module is used by more than 400 services (since we create both development and production environments, actually it’s 800) and we’ve released the module more than 30 versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practices as a Platform Engineer</title>
      <link>https://deeeet.com/posts/practices-as-a-platform-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:41:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeeet.com/posts/practices-as-a-platform-engineer/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been working as a platform engineer (platformer) for almost 5 years. In the previous company, I worked on the internal PaaS based onCloud Foundry and, in the current company, I’ve been working on themicroservices platform based onKubernetes.
Since it&amp;rsquo;s been 5 years, I have some practices which I use for daily decision-making as a platform engineer. In this post, I introduce some of them. The things I listed below are not special and you’ve heard or seen some of these things somewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
