<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Taichi Nakashima</title>
    <link>https://deeeet.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Taichi Nakashima</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja-jp</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-2020 Taichi Nakashima</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 22:03:16 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://deeeet.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Practices for Better Terraform Module</title>
      <link>https://deeeet.com/posts/practices-for-better-terraform-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 22:03:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeeet.com/posts/practices-for-better-terraform-module/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been working at the internal platform team at Mercari for 3 years. In that team, we’ve developed and provided the special Terraform module, which bootstraps required infrastructure and SaaS services for building one microservice, to internal developers (See more details on Terraform Ops for Microservices). Now, this module is used by more than 400 services (since we create both development and production environments, actually it’s 800) and we’ve released the module more than 30 versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practices as a Platform Engineer</title>
      <link>https://deeeet.com/posts/practices-as-a-platform-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:41:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeeet.com/posts/practices-as-a-platform-engineer/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been working as a platform engineer (platformer) for almost 5 years. In the previous company, I worked on the internal PaaS based onCloud Foundry and, in the current company, I’ve been working on themicroservices platform based onKubernetes.
Since it&amp;rsquo;s been 5 years, I have some practices which I use for daily decision-making as a platform engineer. In this post, I introduce some of them. The things I listed below are not special and you’ve heard or seen some of these things somewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
